In this module,
Eğitmen: Bu modülde
we'll take a closer look at the TypeScript Compiler.
TypeScript Derleyicisine daha yakından bakacağız.
Thus far, we always just used it
Şimdiye kadar hep tsc'yi çalıştırıp
by running tsc and then pointing at a file
derlemek istediğimiz dosyayı işaret
which we wanna compile.
ederek kullandık.
Now, whilst that, of course, works,
Şimdi, bu elbette işe yarasa da, birden
it's not really feasible for bigger projects
fazla dosyanızın olduğu veya pratikte görmek istediğiniz
where you have multiple files
her değişiklikten sonra bu komutu çalıştırmak
or where you simply don't want to run this command
istemediğiniz daha büyük projeler için gerçekten
after every change you wanna see in practice.
uygun değildir.
In addition to that convenience,
Şu anda sahip olmadığımız bu kolaylığa
which we currently don't have,
ek olarak, derleme süreciyle
there also are a couple of interesting things
ilgili olarak yapılandırabileceğiniz
you can configure regarding the compilation process
ve aslında neyin derlendiğini ve nasıl derlendiğini
which actually change what is compiled
değiştiren birkaç ilginç şey de var.
And these are therefore the things
Bu nedenle bu modülde bu
we'll take a closer look at in this module.
konulara daha yakından bakacağız.